Security is a hot topic in the news and it’s critically important. BankSouth places the highest value on respecting and protecting the security of your data and transactions. [View our BankSouth Privacy Policy (PDF)](https://banksouth.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/BankSouth-Privacy-Notice-Final-2022-Mar.pdf) or [our BankSouth Mortgage Privacy Policy (PDF),](https://banksouth.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BankSouthMortgage-Privacy-Policy.pdf) and use the quick links below to view security tips, BankSouth’s security statement and additional resources from the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC).

Our primary regulator is the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC). Should you have any questions we cannot adequately answer for you, you can [contact the OCC here](https://www.occ.treas.gov/about/contact-us/general-correspondence/index-contact-us.html).

* * *

BankSouth Digital Privacy and Cookies Policy
--------------------------------------------

_Date most recently updated: January 25, 2022_

#### **Introduction and scope of policy**

Federal law requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to fully understand how we handle user privacy related to our digital presence. This BankSouth Digital Privacy and Cookies Policy (“Policy”) applies to your interaction with BankSouth or any of its subsidiaries (collectively, “BankSouth,” “we,” “us,” “our”): (1) at any online or mobile site or application that we own and control (“Site”), unless a different online and/or mobile or other privacy policy is posted relating to a particular site, application, product, or service, or is made available to you and by its terms supplants this Policy; or (2) via a BankSouth advertisement, page, or account on a third-party site. We may collect, retain, use, and disclose personal and other information about you in accordance with this Policy. Other privacy policies may also apply in addition to the terms of this Policy.

#### **Additional privacy policies and notices**

Certain additional BankSouth privacy-related policies and notices that may apply are posted on the BankSouth Privacy Policy page. The additional policies and notices include the [BankSouth Privacy Notice](https://banksouth.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BankSouth-Privacy-Notice.Final_.2021-October.pdf) (which applies to customers and consumers as described in that notice). Please note that where we have another type of presence on a site owned by a third party, such as a page or handle on a social media site, that third party’s privacy policy and terms of use will apply to the third party’s collection, use, and disclosure of data (rather than this Policy), unless specifically stated otherwise.

#### **Agreement to policy**

To the extent permitted by applicable law, by using a Site or interacting with a BankSouth advertisement or page or account on a third-party site, you consent to this Policy, including your consent to our use and disclosure of information about you in the manner described in this Policy.

#### **Gathering, using, and sharing information**

**Types of information**  
You may interact with us in a variety of ways online, including through a mobile device. We may offer sites or applications that permit browsing and do not require registration. We may also offer the ability to enroll, register or access your accounts online. Information that we may collect about you through online interaction includes information that you input, such as your name, address, email address, and other contact information; data resulting from your activity, such as transaction information and the pages you visit on Site; location information; and biometric information, such as facial recognition, for example, if you choose to enroll in facial recognition. We may also gather additional information, such as the type of device and browser you are using, the IP address of your device, information about your device’s operating system, and additional information associated with your device. We may also gather information collected through cookies, tags, and other technologies, as described further below.

About “cookies” and Ad Choices on third party sites  
Cookies are pieces of data stored on your device. Browser cookies are assigned by a web server to the browser on your device. When you return to a site you have visited before, your browser gives this data back to the server. Mobile applications may also use cookies.

We use cookies and information gathered through their use to make your experience with BankSouth and certain other sites richer and more personalized based on the products, services, or other interactions you have with us and other sites. Information gathered through use of cookies may be used to make offers to you via online ads, email, U.S. mail, or telephone, subject to the privacy preferences you have on file with BankSouth. We also use cookies, sometimes in conjunction with service providers, in online advertising either on our own Site or on third party sites to help determine which of our advertisements are most likely to appeal to you.

If you use multiple browsers or devices, information that we collect about you from one particular browser or device may be used to provide advertising or collect information on another browser or device. Information may also be transferred to a third party for advertising or information collection on behalf of BankSouth. Please note that your choice to opt out on a particular browser or device will apply only to the collection and use of information from that particular browser or device. Opting out on a particular device will not opt you out of information collection on other devices, nor will it limit cross-device sharing on those other devices. If you use different browsers on a device or multiple devices, for each browser and device you wish to opt out, please opt out each device and browser separately at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

Industry standards are currently evolving, and we may not separately respond to or take any action with respect to a “do not track” configuration set in your internet browser.

Other parties that may collect information about your web browsing behavior when you use our Site are generally limited to service providers who may only use any information collected to provide services and marketing for us and not to provide services or advertising for any other party. Note, however, that we also provide certain links on our sites that allow you to interact with third parties who offer additional features, such as allowing web surfers to share information on another platform, such as a social media platform. At other times, information from a third party may be embedded on our Site, such as a map. These features often function through the use of third-party cookies utilized by the third party site, such as a social media platform. As a result, if you use any of these features, these third parties may be able to access information about your web browsing on the pages of our Site where links to these features are in place. You may wish to review information at third party sites, such as social media platforms where you have an account, to determine how these third parties treat data that they obtain with the use of cookies.

We also use cookies for purposes such as maintaining continuity during an online session, gathering data about the use of our Site, monitoring online promotions, and anti-fraud and information security purposes.

#### **Do you have to accept cookies?**

You may be able to set your browser to reject browser cookies. However, if you set your browser options to disallow cookies, you will limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our Site including online banking features and options. The latest versions of internet browsers provide cookie management tools, such as the ability to delete or reject cookies or only retain cookies for a specific browsing session. We recommend that you refer to information supplied by browser providers for more specific information, including how to use these tools.

#### **Additional cookies**

Cookies is a term also used to describe other locally stored objects, such as cookies stored in an Adobe folder on your device. These cookies will not be deleted when you clear cookies from your browser. We may use this technology for purposes such as information security and fraud prevention. We do not use this technology for online behavioral advertising purposes. Please refer to information provided by Adobe for information on how to disable and control Flash objects. If you choose those options, you may limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our Site.

#### **Additional technologies**

We may also use additional technologies such as pixel tags, web beacons, and clear GIFs, and may permit our third-party service providers to use these technologies. We use these technologies for purposes such as measuring the effectiveness of our advertisements or other communications, determining viewing and response rates, and determining which offers to present to you on our own or on third party sites.

#### **Using information**

In addition to the uses described above, we use information for purposes as allowed by law such as: servicing; communicating with you; improving our Site, products, or services; legal compliance; risk control; information security; anti-fraud purposes; marketing or personalizing the presentation of our products and services to you; or tracking email access or website usage, such as number of hits, pages visited, and the length of user sessions in order to evaluate the usefulness of our sites. Location data collected in the background by the BankSouth Mobile Banking App is used to provide location-based messages, offers, and interactions if you have authorized that collection and use in the BankSouth Mobile Banking App and enabled location services on your mobile device.

#### **Sharing**

We may share information with service providers with whom we work, such as data processors and companies that help us market products and services to you. When permitted or required by law, we may share information with additional third parties for purposes including response to legal process. As applicable, please see the additional privacy policies referenced above, such as the BankSouth Privacy Notice, for more information on how we may share information with affiliates and third parties.

#### **Children’s privacy**

Our Sites are not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from such children.

#### **Policy updates and effective date**

If we make updates to this Policy, we will update the Policy with the changes and revise the “date of most recent update” posted at the top of this Policy. Any updates to the Policy become effective when we post the updates on the Site. To the extent permitted by applicable law, your use of the Site following the update to the Policy means that you accept the updated Policy.

* * *

Online Banking Security Statement
---------------------------------

The Online Banking System brings together a combination of industry-approved security technologies to protect data for the bank and for you, our customer. It features password-controlled system entry, a VeriSign-issued Digital ID for the bank’s server, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol for data encryption, a router loaded with a firewall to regulate the inflow and outflow of server traffic.

#### Secure Access and Verifying User Authenticity

To begin a session with the Online Banking server, the user must key in a Log-in ID and a password. Our IBS system uses a “3 strikes and you’re out” lock-out mechanism to deter users from repeated login attempts. After three unsuccessful login attempts, the system locks the user out, requiring either a designated wait period or a phone call to the bank to verify the password before re-entry into the system. Upon successful login, the Digital ID from VeriSign, the experts in digital identification certificates, authenticates the user’s identity and establishes a secure session with that visitor.

#### Secure Data Transfer

Once the server session is established, the user and the server are in a secured environment. Because the server has been certified as a 128-bit secure server by VeriSign, data traveling between the user and the server is encrypted with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. With SSL, data that travels between the Online Banking System and you is encrypted and can only be decrypted with the public and private key pair. In short, the Online Banking server issues a public key to the end user’s browser and creates a temporary private key. These two keys are the only combination possible for that session. When the session is complete, they keys expire and the whole process starts over when a new end user makes a server session. Whenever, SSL is securing your communications, the browser will typically indicate the “secure session” by changing the appearance of a small padlock icon at the bottom of the screen from “open” to “locked.” What this means to you is that your communications are scrambled from your browser to the Online Banking servers at all times, so no unauthorized party can read the information as it is carried over the Internet.

#### Router and Firewall

Requests must filter through a router and firewall before they are permitted to reach the server. A router, a piece of hardware, works in conjunction with the firewall, a piece of software, to block and direct traffic coming to the server. The configuration begins by disallowing ALL traffic and then opens holes only when necessary to process acceptable data requests, such as retrieving web pages or sending customer requests to the Online Banking System.

#### Cookies

During your use of the IBS, the Online Banking System will pass a “cookie” to your browser to identify you. We do not (and cannot) use our cookies to obtain new information about you. A “cookie” is security data given to a browser by a web server and returned by the browser on subsequent transmissions to identify the user and encryption information. When you log onto the system, this cookie enables us to process multiple transactions during the session without you having to provide your Login ID and password for each individual transaction. After a predetermined amount of time set by our security system or when you log off, the session cookie is no longer accepted and the password must be re-entered. A new cookie is used for each session, so that no one can use the cookie to access your account. For Cash Management users, a cookie may also be used to restrict access to a specific PC for conducting business transactions.

#### Phishing

Phishing is a form of e-mail fraud that criminals use to solicit your personal information to steal your identity. These fraudulent e-mails often bear the logo of legitimate businesses and even link to fake corporate websites. BankSouth will NEVER ask for your password or social security number in an e-mail or over the phone. If an e-mail asks for this information delete the email immediately and then run a virus scanner to protect your system.

* * *

Security Tips
-------------

#### Online Banking

Our Online Banking service has several effective security techniques that we encourage you to implement when using Online Banking:

* Never reveal your password to anyone or leave your password anywhere that someone else can obtain or use it.
* Change your password on a regular basis.
* Use the LOGOUT button to end each Online Banking session. Do not use the Back Button to exit the site.
* Change your sessions timeout in User Options to a time that meets your needs.
* Never leave your session without logging out, even for a short time.
* Balance your account on a regular basis using Online Banking to ensure there are no discrepancies.

#### Fraud Protection Related to COVID-19

* Avoid clicking on links in unsolicited emails and be wary of email attachments. See [Using Caution with Email Attachments](https://protect-us.mimecast.com/s/5KkSCDkEqnuB69x4i5PKE7) and [Avoiding Social Engineering and Phishing Scams](https://protect-us.mimecast.com/s/bXmICERQqofWA7qEfpl30D) for more information.
* Use trusted sources—such as legitimate, [government websites](https://protect-us.mimecast.com/s/O0fTCG6KRqtJy78vTQpQZu)—for up-to-date, fact-based information about COVID-19.
* Do not reveal personal or financial information in email, and do not respond to email solicitations for this information.
* Verify a charity’s authenticity before making donations. Review the [Federal Trade Commission’s page on Charity Scams](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0074-giving-charity) for more information.
* Review [CISA Insights](https://www.cisa.gov/sites/default/files/publications/20_0306_cisa_insights_risk_management_for_novel_coronavirus.pdf) on [Risk Management for COVID-19](https://protect-us.mimecast.com/s/t78tCKrE8xiqAo1VSGZSCk) for more information.

* * *

Additional Resources
--------------------
